孩儿们 我曾以为Stella Zinman\n就是与我共度余生的女子
Kids, Stella Zinman was the girl I\nthought I'd spend the rest of my life with.
直到她在圣坛上离我而去\n狠狠地伤透我的心
Until she left me at the altar,\nsmashing my heart to smithereens.
时隔7个月 当我再次碰到她时\n唯一能说的便是
So when I ran into her seven months later,\nthere was only one way to deal with her.
- Stella 真高兴见到你!\n- 我也是
- Stel! Great to see you!\n- You, too.
还有Tony!
And Tony!
真是又惊又喜呀
What a nice surprise.
又惊又喜?
What a nice surprise?
要是有个保险箱从天而降\n把他们砸个稀巴烂 那才叫又惊又喜
No, a nice surprise would be if a safe\nfell from 40 stories and smushed them both.
我是说 你就没做啥出格的?
I mean, you didn't let them have it?
嗯 我们就拉拉家常 然后分道扬镳
No, we had a nice friendly chat, then\nthey went their way and I went mine.
Ted 你搞砸了
Ted, you blew it.
全搞砸了 对吧?
He blew it, right?
干得好 伙计
Well played, sir.
- 好极了\n- 啥?
- Bravo.\n- What?
Robin Ted就该表现得谈定从容
You see, Robin, Ted played it cool,\nwhich is exactly what he should have done.
其实 我觉得你会从...
As a matter of fact, I'd say\non a scale ranging from...
我一直保存着你的毛衣
And I kept this sweater of yours...
有时我久久地躺在浴缸里\n闻着毛衣上你的香味
and sometimes I just sit in the bathtub\nfor hours just, you know, just sniffing it.
到另一个极端...
all the way to...
这是我的未婚妻
This is my new fianc\e.
她是法国版Stella 你也能看出来\n她够丰满吧
She's basically Stella, except she's French\nand, as you can see, she's got enormous cans.
幸会\n(法语)
Enchant\.
幸会
这样你占尽上风
I'd say you nailed it.
我的主意比你的好
I'll do you one better.
你让Stella开始思考
You, sir, got Stella thinking.
"天哪 Ted怎么看上去这么帅啊\n我当初是不是选错人了?"
"Gosh, Ted seemed so cool today.\nDid I choose the wrong guy?"
一周后她就会来找你
Give it a week; you'll get her back.
还有她的"小妹妹"
And her front.
你们感觉到了不?
Oh, did you just feel that?
我想是"太帅"震了下而已
I think we just had a "what up" quake.
我才不要吃回头草 也不要她的"小妹妹" \n我只想往前看
I don't want her back. Or her\nfront. I just want to move on.
这是重要的一步
And this was an\nimportant st towards that.
迈向新生活
To moving on.
我是说真的
And you know, I really meant it.
但那晚 我还是开始胡思乱想
But still, that night,\nmy mind began to wander.
- 我真是大错特错\n- 我知道
- I made a terrible mistake.\n- I know.
我的人品比你好得多
I'm a better person than you are.
绝对是这样
You totally are.
我们重归于好 让爱爱来得更猛烈些吧
Let's get back together and\nhave way more sex than before.
好!
Deal!
你好 Ted
Hello, Ted.
老爸老妈浪漫史\n第四季 第23集
How I Met Your\nMother Season04 Episode23
进来吧 没什么尴尬的
No, come in. It's not weird at all.
Ted Teddy Ted Ted Ted\nTed, Teddy Ted Ted Ted.
我就知道不该夺人所爱
I knew it was wrong to\nsteal somebody's fianc\e.
我是说 我现在烦恼不已 夜夜难眠
I mean, I grappled with\nit. I was up nights.
不是因为好事才睡不着\n(做爱算好事咩 Barney说当然算)
And not for the good reason.
当然有时候也的确是在做好事
Well, sometimes for the good reason.
我是说 我和Stella 5年没见面了
I mean, Stella and I hadn't seen\neach other in five years, so,
你能想象 一开始爱是那么炽热激荡
as you can imagine, the beginning,\nit was just fast and furious.
屋子里天崩地裂\n看到这里都秃了一块不?
Lamps breaking, furniture\nmoving. You see this bald patch?
- 嗯 Tony...\n- 总之我们迈向了新生活
- Yeah, Tony...\n- Anywaywe moved on.
我 Lucy Stella\n我们本打算搬去洛杉矶
Me, Lucy, Stella-- we\nwere gonna move to L.A.
我打算做编剧
I was gonna become a screenwriter.
然后我们遇到你 你看上去这么...悲伤
Then we bumped into you, and\nyou just looked so... sad.
悲伤? 没 我认为\n你们所说的悲伤是指毫不介意
Sad? No. I-I think what you're calling\nsad was actually a jovial nonchalance.
Ted 你看上去糟透了
Ted, you looked awful, okay?
就像只受伤的小猎狗\n蜷缩在货车的角落
Like a little dachshund puppy with a bad back\nthat's got to pull itself around on a cart.
你到底来干吗?
Why are you here?
听着 Ted 我知道我来很冒昧
Look, Ted, I know I can\ncome across pretty tough,
但我实在不能对你的悲伤视而不见
but I can't bear to have hurt\nsomeone the way I hurt you.
我觉得是命运安排我们在街角相遇
I think fate put me on that\ncorner to make this right.
当然我无法弥补Stella对你造成的伤害
Obviously, I can't fill that giant\ncrater that Stella left in your heart.
我一直有约会 马不停蹄
I've been dating. Like, a lot.
随后我听说被炒鱿鱼
And then I heard you got fired.
我现在自己开了家小公司
I transitioned into\nsmall business ownership.
私有企业可是经济支柱
It's the backbone of the economy.
不 才不是 \nTed 我的家族大大有钱
No, it's not. Ted, my\nfamily's got a lot of money.
我想用那些钱来补偿你
And I want to use that money\nto make this right with you.
Tony很有钱?
Tony is rich?
Ted Ted 告诉我他给你开了支票
Oh, Ted. Oh, Ted, tell\nme he wrote you a check.
他给你开了张大额支票
Tell me he wrote you a big, fat check.
支票太肥 它想游泳都脱不下衣服
A check so big it doesn't take its\nshirt off when it goes swimming.
那支票确实够肥
Ha, that is a big, fat check.
支票太肥 要是你和它上了床\n都不好意思跟自个哥们说
A check so big, if you had sex with\nit, you wouldn't tell your buddies.
那支票确实够肥
That is a big, fat check.
支票太肥 要是你乘飞机坐它旁边
A check so big that when you\nsit next to it on an airplane,
你会想这支票为啥不订两个座呢
you find yourself wondering whether\nthe check should have bought two seats.
- 那...支票真是肥!\n- 嗯
- That... Is a big, fat check!\n- Yeah!
他没给我开支票
He didn't write me a check.
- Ted 我想帮你找份工作\n- 工作?
- Ted, I want to offer you a job.\n- A job?
每年我的家族都会赞助哥伦比亚大学\n一大笔钱 所以我有些门路
Every year, my family gives a lot of money\nto Columbia University, so I got some pull.
你觉得设计...
How would you like to design...
我的心快跳到喉咙口 图书馆? 学生中心?
My heart leapt into my throat. A\nnew library? A new student center?
你自己的教案 当建筑学教授怎么样?
your very own curriculum as\na professor of architecture.
不 谢谢
No, thanks.
"不 谢谢"是啥意思?
What do you mean, "No, thanks"?
Ted 你会成为杰出的教授 好吧?
Ted, you would be a\ngreat professor, okay?
你博学多识 出口成章 要是你愿意
You are knowledgeable, you're a\ngood talker, and when you need to,
还能蓄上帅呆的大胡子
you can grow a very handsome neck beard.
我不想做教授
I'm not gonna be a professor.
当你的事业跌至谷底又得付账单时
Teaching architecture is what you do\nwhen your career has totally bottomed out
才选择去教建筑学
and you need to pay the bills.
我可是小老板 经济的支柱
Small business owner.\nBackbone of the economy.
我不做那工作也会活得很好
I'm not gonna take that job, all\nright? I'm gonna be just fine.
- 换个话题\n- 好 换个话题
- New topic.\n- Okay, new topic.
我今天收到张200块的超速罚单
I just got a $200 speeding ticket today.
真逊 老兄 你就不能\n花言巧语蒙混过去吗?
Oh, that sucks, dude. You\ncouldn't talk your way out of it?
没法蒙混过去
You can't talk your way out of a ticket.
我就成功过 那时是... 是1998年
I've done it. It was--\nwhat was it? -- it was 1998.
明尼苏达州 1998年
******\n- So where's the fire?\n- There's no fire.
- 你是要去救火么？\n- 没有着火
其实 我正要去烧烤的地方点着火\n也没啥特别的啦
Actually, uh, you know, there is a fire at\nthis barbecue I'm headed to. Nothing special.
汉堡 排骨...腊肠啦
Burgers, ribs... brats.
孩子 你知道这么开多危险...
Son, do you have any idea\nhow dangerous it is to be...
- 你说腊肠?\n- 嗯 腊肠
- Did you say brats?\n- Yeah, brats.
我妈把它们泡在比利时啤酒中两天了 也没啥啦
My mom marinates them in Belgian\nbeer for two days. No big.
说也奇怪 有根厚实多汁
Funny thing was, I could've sworn\nthat one of those thick, succulent,
的熏腊肠上面有字
hickory-smoked brats\nhad some writing on it.
真奇怪 你刚说啥?
Weird. Anyways, what were you saying?
上面写了啥? 腊肠上?
What-what did it say? The brat?
写了"明尼苏达州\nJorgensen警官专有" 你...
It said "Property of Minnesota\nState Trooper Jorgensen." You a...
你就是腊肠男 Jorgensen警官?
you a brat man, Officer Jorgensen?
你要去这里吗?
You going to this address?
跟紧我 拉响警笛 我们得闯几个红灯
Follow me and lean on the horn.\nWe're gonna be running some reds.
切
Well, duh.
我也会 要是我也正赶去烧烤的话
I would've done that, too, if\nI'd have been going to a barbecue.
我靠 我就是啊
Damn, I was.
看吧 得先摸清你的敌人
See, it's all about\nsizing up your opponent.
我能看出那警官喜欢腊肠 因为
I could tell that the officer\nwas a brat man because, well,
没走几步路他就喘不过气来\n还有枪套上有芥末
he was out of breath just from walking to\nmy car and he had mustard on his holster.
Marshall Eriksen!\nMarshall Eriksen!
仅凭腊肠就搞定巡警
Manipulating an officer of\nthe law with your sausage.
简直酷毙啦
That is very hot.
你觉得我不能蒙混过去?
You think I can't talk\nmy way out of a ticket?
我可是Barney Stinson\n操纵万物的主人
I am Barney Stinson,\nmaster of manipulation.
我都能让舞娘付我脱衣舞的钱
If I can talk a stripper into\npaying me for a lap dance,
我觉得我能蒙混过去
I think I can talk my\nway out of a ticket.
接受挑战 等下
Challenge accep--\nWait for it.
我不明白
I don't get it.
"Ted"(accepTed后三个字母) 接受
Oh, "Ted." AcceTed.
现在明白啦
I get it now.
- 又想怎么样?\n- 你想做建筑师? 很好
- What now?\n- You want to be an architect? Great.
我知道有家私立学校要造新楼
Guy I went to private school\nwith wants a new house built.
要是你愿意 这活就是你的
Job's yours if you want it.
Tony 听着 我不需要你帮忙
Tony, look, I don't need your help.
这是他开的价
Here's's what he's offering you.
这支票真够肥
That is a big, fat check.
好戏上场\n(修太木)
Showtime.
驾照和登记证明
License and registration.
当然 警官 马上
Oh, of course, Officer. Right away.
先生 这是定制意大利西装的礼券
Sir, this is a gift certificate\nfor a custom-tailored Italian suit.
现在没事了吧?
So, we done here?
375块!
$375!
- 他还拿走了礼券\n- 天哪
- And he kept the gift certificates.\n- Oh, man.
我要打电话给Emilio\n让他给他裆部那里做得紧点
I'm gonna call Emilio and tell him\nto short-sheet him on the crotch.
这个你可不太在行 伙计
You are bad at this, dude.
得了吧 Robin
Oh, whatever, Robin.
好像你蒙混得过去一样
Like you've ever talked\nyour way out of a ticket.
你说笑呢吧? Robin可是美女\n美女不会吃罚单
Are you kidding me? Robin's a pretty\ngirl. Pretty girls don't get tickets.
我敢说Robin被叫停了无数次\n但从没吃过罚单
I bet Robin's been pulled over tons\nof times, never once gotten a ticket.
这话可真不厚道!
That is outrageous!
但却是事实
And factual.
驾照和登记...
License and regis...
宝贝 别别别 别哭
Oh, honey. Oh, no, no, no, don't cry.
没事 不开罚单
It's okay. No ticket for you.
下次开慢点 好吗?
Just, uh, go a little\nslower next time, okay?
- 嗯\n- 好
- Yeah.\n- Okay.
谢谢
Thank you.
耶!
Yeah!
失陪一下 我想\n我有东西落在新泽西了
Excuse me. I think I left\nsomething in New Jersey.
和富人的午饭吃得咋样?
How did your lunch go with the rich guy?
开始还不错
Well, uh, it started off great.
我想设计套房子来映衬\n保护完好的自然环境
I want to design a house that celebrates\nthe landscape without overpowering it.
Frank Lloyd Wright
在1935年设计流水别墅时...
You know, when Frank Lloyd Wright\ndesigned Fallingwater in 1935, there's...
嗯 嗯 无需多说
Yes, yes, that's all fine.
我相信你的实力
I'm sure you'll do a great job.
其实我关心的是地下室
What I'm really worried\nabout is the basement.
特别是洗衣房
Specifically the laundry room.
洗衣房?
The laundry room?
我要一个15英尺长15英尺宽的洗衣房
I require a laundry room\nof 15 feet by 15 feet,
从地板到天花板都贴满抗污瓷砖
stain-proof ceramic tile\nfrom floor to ceiling.
我喜欢自己洗衣服 有时弄得乱七八糟
I'm a man who likes to do his own\nlaundry, and sometimes, it gets messy.
- 乱七八糟?\n- 乱七八糟
- Messy?\n- Messy.
天花板上吊根9英尺长的铁链
Steel chains will dangle from the\nceiling at a height of nine feet.
洗衣服之前我会把洗衣袋吊在上面...
And that is where my laundry bags will hang\nfor three days and three nights before I...
三天三夜
clean them.
呃 Ted 听...听起来这家伙\n像是在要求你帮他设计...
Uh, Ted, it-it kind of sounds like\nwhat this guy is asking you to design...
- 虐杀室\n- 简直就是个虐杀室
- It's a murder house.\n- It is. It's totally a murder house.
知道吗 作为一个武术家 \n必须要相信自己的直觉
You know, as a martial artist,\nI'm trained to trust my instincts,
而我的直觉告诉我这间地下室...
and my instincts are saying this...
棒极了
feels very good.
这牛扒太生了
The steak is so rare.
是吧? 是吧?
Right? Right?
最后一个要求: 隔音效果
One final concern: soundproofing.
洗衣服的时候 我通常会很吵
I tend to make a lot of\nracket when I launder.
我示范一下吧
I'll show you what I mean.
现在我去洗衣房 \n你试试能不能听到我的声音
I'm gonna go to my laundry room,\nand you tell me if you can hear me.
Tony... 这家伙是不是有点怪怪的?
Tony... does something\nfeel off about this guy?
没错 终于走了 居然溜了!
Yeah. Off the hook!
兄弟 这单生意你肯定成
Bro, you are nailing this.
- Ted 你可不能设计虐杀室呀!\n- 我才不会设计虐杀室呢
- Ted, you can't design a murder house!\n- I'm not gonna design a murder house.
- Ted 你可不能设计虐杀室呀!\n- 我才不会设计虐杀室呢!
- Ted, you can't design a murder house!\n- I'm not gonna design a murder house!
好戏上场
Bring it.
长官拜托你 我老婆快要生宝宝了!
Officer, please, my wife\nis about to have a baby!
- 她羊水破了!\n- 你老婆哪儿呢?
- Her water just broke!\n- Where's your wife?
她乘另一辆车
She took the other car.
这可是意大利皮革 你知道啦...
This is Italian leather, so... I...
噢 别...
Oh, come...
虐杀室那档事 真不好意思
I'm sorry about that murder house thing.
我的错 好嘛 东家不做做西家
That was my bad. That's\non me. So, new plan.
朋友 你 将要给自由女神建一个丈夫
You, my friend, are gonna build\nthe Statue of Liberty a husband.
- 市政厅里我有人\n- Tony 够了!
- Now, I got some suction down at City Hall.\n- Tony, stop it!
我不需要你帮忙 你没必要这样
I don't want your help, okay?\nYou don't have to do this.
- 当然有必要\n- 为啥?
- Yes, I do.\n- Why?
因为...
Because...
你跟Stella好那阵子 \n我深深地思念她
when you were with Stella,\nI know how much I missed her.
我能明白你现在的感觉
I can only imagine\nyou feel the same way.
那你就安心吧
Okay, well, let me\nput your mind at ease.
我没想过要Stella回来
I don't want Stella back, okay?
她欺骗了我 在婚礼时放我鸽子
She lied to me and left me at the altar.
什么人呀这是?
What kind of person does that?
没了她我还快活呢
I'm better off without her.
她是你的了 哥们
She's all yours, buddy.
有你的 那我放宽心了
There you go. Load off my mind.
就这样
And that was it.
Tony走了 我也准备就这样让事情过去
Tony left, and I began to put\nthis whole business far behind me.
至少我是这么想的
Or so I thought.
Stella\nStella.
Tony跟我分手了
Tony broke up with me.
Tony跟你分手了?
Okay, Tony broke up with you?
他说是因为你跟他聊了些事
He said it was because\nof something you said.
你让Tony甩了Stella?
You got Tony to dump Stella?
我很遗憾 可帅小伙干得好哇
I am very sorry, but I'm going to\nhave to insist that you bump this.
咱们在走廊上谈吧
Let's, um, let's talk out in the hall.
等你回来庆祝哦
It'll be waiting.
为啥你会来?
So, why are you here?
Ted 已经七个月 我知道已经太迟了\n事情是这样的
Look, Ted, this is about seven\nmonths too late, but here goes.
Tony跟我在高中就开始拍拖
I've been in love with\nTony since high school.
咱们的关系维持了很久 可后来我怀孕了
We dated for a long time,\nbut then I got pregnant,
当时我们都只有19岁 这对我们太沉重了\n所以我们分手了
and I guess for two 19-year-olds it was\njust too much to handle, so we broke up.
然后很长的时间里 \n我专心做好母亲的角色
And for a long time I just\nfocused on being a mother.
忘记Tony 忘记...
I forgot about Tony. I forgot about...
如何去爱
the very idea of being in love.
是你闯进我的生活 唤醒我的爱
And then you came along\nand reminded me. And...
我就是爱上了你这点
I loved you for that.
我爱你太深 怎么都爱不够
I loved you so much, in fact,\nthat it was just shy of enough.
但我对Tony的爱从未停止
But I never stopped loving Tony.
原谅他吧 亲爱的 他知道错了
Take him back, honey. He's sorry.
不 事情...事情不是这样的
No, that's-that's not...\nthat's not what's happening.
回屋子里去吧 Matsen太太
Just go back inside, Mrs. Matsen.
见到你很高兴 Stella
It was good seeing you, Stella.
你能劝劝Tony吗??
Can you talk to Tony?
什么?
What?
他会听你的 解铃还须系铃人
He'd listen to you. You changed\nhis mind. You could change it back.
我知道这样要求你很过分...
I know it's an awful thing to ask...
没错 确实很过分
Yeah, it's an awful thing to ask.
我不知道该怎么办了 好吗?
Well, I don't know\nwhat else to do, okay?
我爱他
I love him.
噢 原来你爱的是他 \n然后还想要我同情你?
Oh, you love him. So what, you're-you're\nappealing to the romantic in me?
这就是你的策略?
Is that your strategy?
那人已经走了
Because that guy's gone.
你已经拉不回来了
You can't pull those strings anymore.
就是因为你 他没有任何羁绊
They're not attached to\nanything thanks to you.
去吧 亲爱的 亲他!
Go ahead, honey, kiss him!
- 给我回去! Matsen太太\n- Matsen太太 回去!
- Go inside, Mrs. Matsen!\n- Mrs. Matsen, go inside!
你能行! 你能行!
Okay, you can do this. You can do this!
噢 你肯定行
Oh, you can do this.
- 请出示执照和登记证...\n- 请出示执照和登记证明
- License and regis...\n- License and registration.
什么?
Excuse me?
像你这么漂亮的脸蛋 我想也得要个执照吧
I can only assume you need a license\nto have a face that beautiful.
还有这具娇躯?
And that body?
这么爆炸性的身材 \n估计要登记注册以防万一
I'm guessing something that explosive has\nto be registered with the proper authorities.
- 下车\n- 怎么了 我被捕了吗?
- Get out of the car.\n- Why, am I under arrest?
不是...
No...
不过你要被上了
but you're about to be under me.
才不是 你瞎掰的
No. False. Did not happen.
那是A片的情节 那A片我看过
That's a line from a\nporno. I've seen that porno.
甚至连我的春梦都出现过这情节
Hell, I've made that porno.
你们就不知道 \n我的人生与A片间的不同之处
When will you guys realize that the only\ndifference between my real life and a porno
只在于我的人生更加精彩吗?
is my real life has better lighting?
你在撒谎
You're lying.
我没撒谎!
I am not lying!
我以我老母的名义起誓
I swear on my mother.
我以歌利亚国家银行的名义起誓
I swear on Goliath National Bank.
我以我西服的名义起誓
I swear on my suits.
我... 没... 撒... 谎
I... am... not... lying.
他在撒谎 事实是这样的
He was lying. Here's\nwhat really happened.
去吧 亲爱的 亲他
Go ahead, honey, kiss him.
- 给我回去! Matsen太太\n- Matsen太太 回去!
- Go inside, Mrs. Matsen!\n- Mrs. Matsen, go inside!
你要我怎么做才肯帮我?
Is there anything I can\ndo to make this better?
不帮
No.
大家快来商场吧!\n(Robin成名曲... 笑翻)
Let's go to the mall, everybody!
- 喂\n- Ted 是我! Barney 是我!
- Hello.\n- Ted, it's me! It's Barney It's me!
快帮帮我! 我惹大麻烦了!
I need your help! I'm in big trouble!
慢点讲 怎么了?
Whoa-whoa-whoa, slow\ndown. What happened?
这么爆炸性的身材 \n估计要登记注册以防万一
I'm guessing something that explosive has\nto be registered with the proper authorities.
- 下车\n- 怎么了 我被捕了吗?
- Get out of the car.\n- Why, am I under arrest?
没错 我查过你
Yes, you are. I ran your plates.
最近三天 你有15次违反交通法规记录
You've had 15 moving violations\nin the last three days.
下车
Get out of the car.
等等 我老婆快要生宝宝了!
But no, my wife's having a baby!
- 我有条香肠 上面有你的名字!\n- 立刻下车!
- I have a sausage with your name on it!\n- Out of the car now!
快来新泽西 布拉柴维尔监狱保释我\n(刚果首都... 什么破名)
I need you to come to Brazzaville,\nNew Jersey and bail me out.
我有事不能抽身
I'm kind of in the middle of something.
Ted 快
Hurry, Ted.
他们把我跟超残忍的罪犯关在一起
You have no idea of the kind of the hardened\ncriminals they've got me in here with.
你们会把油漆喷雾给回我们吗?
Are we gonna get our spray paint back?
快救我! Ted\n(Barney你个小样)
Save me, Ted!
你想要弥补是吗?
You want to do something for me?
- 我要人载我去新泽西\n- 好的
- I need a ride to New Jersey.\n- Okay.
过关费你给 是不? \n开玩笑啦
You'll pay for tolls,\nright? I'm kidding.
就这样我和Stella一路驶去新泽西
So Stella and I drove all\nthe way out to New Jersey,
把你们Barney叔叔保释出来 \n再一路驶回家
bailed your Uncle Barney out of\njail and drove all the way home.
还有 Ted 你现在约会的那妞怎样了?
Oh, by the way, Ted, how's\nthat girl you've been seeing?
那个超辣的巨乳法国妞
That super hot French chick\nwith the big enormous boobs?
你是说Claudette? 她...她还好啦
Oh, you mean Claudette?\nShe's, uh, she's fine.
好家伙 那是你处过最辣的妞 \nTed 最辣的!
Man, she's the hottest girl you\nhave ever been with, Ted. Ever!
拜了 Stella
Bye, Stella.
Ted...\nTed...
我再一次说对不起
I'm so sorry again about everything.
- 我应该...\n- 我会去劝Tony
- For what it's worth...\n- I'll talk to Tony.
真的?
Really?
我希望你能幸福 Stella
I want you to be happy, Stella.
我会去劝他
I'll talk to him.
我去劝了
And I did.
跟他说了什么我忘了
I don't remember what I said to him,
不过我猜我让他回心转意了\n因为第二天他们就飞去加利福利亚
but I guess I changed his mind because\nthe next day, they flew to California.
Stel重新开了间整形美容所
Stel set up a new dermatology practice.
无独有偶 Tony成为了一个编剧家
And against all odds, Tony found\nsome success as a screenwriter.
他的作品 "婚礼新娘" 火爆异常
His movie, The Wedding\nBride, was a big hit.
这迟点再说
But we'll get to that later.
不过告诉我 为什么选择Tony?
Okay, but just tell me this. Why Tony?
因为他的钱 他的练功服? 还是什么?
I mean, is it the money, the kung\nfu pajamas? Like, what... what is it?
他是命中注定的那个人
He's the one.
命中注定
The one.
我知道有点无稽 不过 是真的
Yeah, I know it's\nkinda sappy, but, yeah.
我要说些话 最近压抑了很久没说的话
Okay, I'm gonna say something out loud that I've been\ndoing a pretty good b of not saying out loud lately.
你和Tony之间所拥有的...\n我一度以为我们之间会有的...
What you and Tony have-- what I\nthought for a second you and I had...
我s所知Marshall和Lily之间有的...那一切
what I know that\nMarshall and Lily have...
我很渴望拥有 真的
I want that. I do.
我一直在等 一直在等 不过...
I keep waiting for it to happen\nand waiting for it to happen, and...
可能是 嗯...
I guess I'm just, um...
可能是我已经厌倦等待了吧
I'm tired of waiting.
这就是我对此唯一想说的了
And that is all I'm going\nto say on that subject.
知道吗 我讲过我有次蒙混过关被免开罚单吗?
You know, I once talked my\nway out of a speeding ticket?
真的?
Really?
那次是回父母家 在国道上飙到了90英里
I was heading upstate to my parents'\nhouse doing, like, 90 on this country road,
被警察截停了 那警察走出车
and I got pulled over. So\nthis cop gets out of his car.
他有点装腔作势 \n说"小妞 我在这等你一整天了"
He kind of swaggers on over and he's, like,\n"Young lady, I have been waiting for you all day."
我看着他 \n说"不好意思 警官 我已经尽快赶来了"
So I looked up at him and I said, "I'm so\nsorry, Officer. I got here as fast as I could."
真事?
For real?
不是 是个老笑话
No. It's an old joke.
我明白你已经厌倦等待 \n而且可能还要等上一段日子
I know thayou're tired of waiting, and\nyou may have to wait a little while more,
不过你的真命天女正赶来呢 Ted
but she's on her way, Ted.
她正尽快赶来
And she's getting here\nas fast as she can.
再见 Stella
Bye, Stella.
再见 Ted
Good-bye, Ted.
她通过电话簿两天后找到了我\n(那个女警察)
tracked me down two days\nlater using a phone book.
那是我最后一次在内裤上签名
And that's the last time I wrote\nmy name in my undergarments.
- 嘿 Lily! 你回来了!
- Lily!\n- Hey, Lily!You're back!\n- Lily!
Barney 刚开始听到\n你说的那个花生酱玩笑
Barney, when you told me that\npeanut butter and jam joke,
我觉得超恶心
I was completely disgusted.
可今早我洗澡时 \n我突然想明白 真的很好笑
But I was in the shower this morning and it\npopped into my head and it actually made me laugh.
花生酱
Peanut butter.
所以我想明白 我是反应过度了
So I can see now how\nI may have overreacted.
Marshall说的 不是我
Marshall's words, not mine.
- 很高兴再见到你 Lily\n- 谢谢
- Well, it's good to see you again, Lily.\n- Thanks.
你们在聊点啥呢?
So what have you been up to?
我要去健忘症康复所\n带着一沓我"孩子"的照片和结婚戒指
I'm going to an amnesia ward with a bunch\nof photos of my children and a wedding ring.
找一个最辣的病人作为我妻子 咱们...
I'm gonna find the hottest\npatient/my wife, and we are going...
快乐的时光过得特别快 又是时候说掰掰
Okay, so that's good enough for tonight.
我要回去好好消化这段 明天见
I gotta ease back into\nthis. See ya tomorrow.